Under the unction and instruction of the Holy Spirit,
Prophet T.B. Joshua ministers to people within The SCOAN auditorium.
Among them is this man who instantly reacts as the power of God flows through his body.
Every unclean spirit that operated in his life is now bowing and submitting
to the superior authority in the name of Jesus Christ.
Let's watch what happens next.
You are addicted to drugs.
Yes.
It's an addiction.
You took the drugs and you carried the drugs.
This is an addiction. If care is not taken, you will live the rest of your life in prison.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer
And Deliverance In Jesus' Name
He's free.
Set Free In Jesus' Name
He is free indeed from the spirit of addiction. Glory be to God!
TESTIMONY TIME
My name is Geronimo, and I come from a small country in Europe.
My testimony goes like this:
It happened when the man of God touched me and prophesied that I was into hard drugs
and it was one hundred percent true.
From that moment, the bad spirit left me
and the urge for drugs and to be back in the criminal life, went away.
It all started when I was the age of 15 or 16; I started selling marijuana.
At the age of 17 or 18, I started selling cocaine.
After that, I started selling guns and carrying guns myself.
That was when I became a part of organised crime.
I was especially trafficking cocaine in different parts of Europe.
So, our brother is explaining how from a very young age, he got involved in these criminal activities.
Apart from trafficking these drugs, you were also taking these drugs yourself.
Yes, I was also sometimes taking the drugs myself
and that led me to a lifestyle where all the money I got, only went for bad things.
So, you said, every money you received through this, you would use it for bad things.
Could you give us an example of how you were living your life at this period?
All the money was spent on prostitutes, parties, expensive cars, holidays, and not good things.
I paid to have tattoos made.
So, our brother is explaining that everything - the finances he made
from these illicit activities - he ended up using them for very bad things
such as visiting prostitutes, clubbing and other such things -
even tattooing various tattoos across his body.
So, as you were engaging in this - tell us, brother, more about your story,
how the spirit pushed you to these criminal activities.
Yes, it pushed me really hard.
I was especially focused on trafficking cocaine.
Mostly, I went to countries with a harbour; that is where we would get it.
We trafficked it with a strong magnet under cars on the motorblock.
If the police caught us, someone would hide it there.
It was mostly one-day trips back to my country - one day there, one night sleeping, one day back,
then distributing the drugs.
That lifestyle took me to Thailand to prison.
So, our brother is saying that it even got to the extent that he went to prison in Thailand.
How did you now come to a point where you realised you needed to stop such activities?
That was at the age of 25 or 26.
I began to realise that I could not go further with that because nothing good came from that life.
I started to slow down but still, there was something that pushed me every time.
When I wanted to slow down or quit everything, I couldn't help myself.
Finally, the only solution was Jesus Christ.
Hallelujah. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
So, our brother is explaining how he realised he needed to stop this lifestyle
but there was a force pushing him and he could not stop on his own.
So, brother, could you just tell us - at this point, you were taking these drugs as well -
as you were engaging in the trafficking, you were also taking the drugs.
How did that addiction to the drugs affect your own health and life?
It affected my health; I was not able to train which I did before.
I started taking some drugs daily.
You have said that it reached a point where you were taking some of these drugs on a daily basis.
Now, how did you discover this church in the midst of this?
How did you find out about The SCOAN?
When I started wanting to slow down, I started watching YouTube.
One day when I was watching YouTube, Emmanuel TV popped up on the first page.
There was a video about a drug trafficker from Libya.
It touched my heart and I became nearly addicted to watching Emmanuel TV.
So, you were not looking for that video? As you were on YouTube, the video just popped up
and you saw a video of a testimony of someone who was also a drug trafficker
who was delivered here in The SCOAN and that really touched you.
Yes.
Glory be to God Almighty.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
And, brother, to the glory of God, you finally came to The SCOAN.
Just tell us what happened when you came.
After watching Emmanuel TV for three years, finally, I came here.
When I came to The SCOAN and wanted to take my drugs out, they had disappeared.
Brother, since you arrived in the church and received that word of prophecy and deliverance,
just tell us the changes in your life.
The urge and the push is finally gone.
Everything that pushed me before to do criminal things or take drugs is finally gone.
I have no urge for smoking or drinking.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Wow! We give all the glory to God Almighty.
Brother, we believe you are really in a position to advise people.
Especially those who are still taking drugs, are involved in such activities as trafficking drugs.
As you are here right now, what is your word of advice?
My word of advice: Nothing good comes out from drugs.
I can only advise never to go into that life because you will just lose everything you have.
There comes nothing good from it.
So, you are advising people that if they are into such a lifestyle or taking such things -
what should they do to receive solution and freedom?
The only way I got my problem solved was at The SCOAN in Lagos, Nigeria, through Jesus Christ!
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
I think what our brother is really emphasizing is that he had tried on his own to stop
but there was a force beyond his control that was really pushing him into that life,
once he got involved at such a young age.
But today, he is delivered through the prayer and prophecy of Prophet T.B. Joshua.
And he is advising people that if anyone is having a similar issue,
they need to seek deliverance in the name of Jesus Christ
to be separated from the evil spirit behind such an addiction or such activities.
Today, he is a living testimony to the glory of God.
Brother, we thank God for your life. We pray that God will give you the grace to maintain this deliverance
by making the Word of God the standard for your life
and we believe the best is yet to come in your life, in Jesus' name.
Amen.
One more time, let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
TESTIMONY CONTINUES
Hello. My name is Geronimo, and I come from a small country in Europe.
I came to The SCOAN two weeks ago.
The man of God touched me and for the first time, prophesied to me, on Sunday
and he was very right in his prophecy that I was into hard drugs and had a criminal past.
After that, he prayed for me and delivered me and I feel good.
From 15 to 29, I lived a criminal life, with ups and downs.
You can never get anything good out of a criminal life.
I was into drug trafficking an dmore.
I operated in different parts of Europe and was involved in organised crime.
I was sitting at home and one day, as I was watching YouTube,
Emmanuel TV popped up on the first page and I started to watch it.
Since that day, I have been watching it nearly every day.
After three years of watching Emmanuel TV, I finally arrived here.
Ok. So, since after your deliverance last Sunday, can you please share with us -
what are the changes and the transformation that has taken place in your life?
Everything has changed - no more pain, no more urge for bad things,
no urge for drugs, smoking, criminal things. Everything has gone.
Now, I can focus on God's will, the good side of life and forget about the past.
I am totally delivered, in Jesus' name.
We thank God Almighty for your life.
Now, we can see you making preparations - you are going back to your country, right?
Yes.
What message are you taking back to your country?
I can say to everyone - if you have the same problem I had which I came here with,
involve God who is really at work here. I have never been in a place like this before.
This was my first time and I can say that God is really at work here.
So now that you are going back to your country,
the man of God wants to make a meaningful contribution to your life,
apart from the deliverance you have received through the grace of God
in the life of the anointed man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua.
The man of God has also decided, with the support of the Emmanuel TV Partners,
to bless you with the cash sum of 2,000 USD.
This is the money, for you to be able to reestablish yourself
in going into a new business and forgetting about your past
and having no reason to go back to your past anymore
and 'The Mirror' book from the anointed man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua, and Emmanuel TV Partners.
Thank you, Man of God, for everything you have done for me
and to the Emmanuel TV Team and Partners, thank you very much for everything.
For this 2,000 USD and 'The Mirror' book, I can go back to my country and start a new life
and make everything well.
I am very grateful for everything.
Thank You, Jesus!
Thank you very much. On behalf of the anointed man of God and the Emmanuel TV Partners,
thank you also for accepting this cash gift and we know this is also going to transform your life
and with this money, you will start a new business.
We believe that very soon, you are coming back here to give glory to God Almighty
for the great transformation that will begin to take place in your life
after this deliverance you have received, in Jesus' name.
Amen!
Thank You, Jesus!